

# **Profile**

Tech Stack: Java • Spring • JavaScript • HTML • CSS • Flexbox • Grid • TDD • Agile (Scrum) • Object Oriented Programming (OOP) • JSON • Restful APIs • Responsive Design / Mobile • Structured Query Language (SQL) • Relational Databases • Source Control / Git • React • NodeJS

\_\_\_\_\_

For 25 years, I've been learning computer technology. I've always had an interest in computers. Then I went onto MRI machines, 3D printing, and computer programming. A very quick and enthusiastic learner who quickly acclimates to a new environment.

# **Employment History**

#### **Software Consultant**

JUNE 2021 - PRESENT

Maintaining website's for private clients.

- Effectively coded software changes and alterations based on specific design specifications.
  - Java/HTML/Javascript/CSS

#### Broker/IT Associate, Morris Pawnshop

NOVEMBER 2016 - JANUARY 2022

Developed website, managed items and added features when needed. Fixing hardware issues, network issues, tech issues generally.

• Java/HTML/CSS/Javascript

### MRI Engineer/Field Technician, Ohio Valley Medical Systems

MAY 2014 - JULY 2016

- Created databases for complete inventory systems.
- Maintained the warehouse shipping
- Logged hospital PM reports/sent them to sites that requested PM Reports for the Department of Health when needed.
- Performed Preventative Maintenance for MRI Machines as well as diagnosis and repairs.
  - Java/HTML/CSS/Spring

## Education

# Computer Programming/Programmer, General, We Can Code IT, Cleveland, OH

JANUARY 2022 - APRIL 2022

Full stack development course focusing on Java, HTML, CSS, JSON, JavaScript, Github, Spring Framework

#### **Details**

331 Waterside Ave Canal Fulton, 44614 Ohio Ohio 330-257-8539 dallasjbaldwin@gmail.com

### Links

Linkedin.com/dallas-baldwin